Edgar Fernandez

San Diego, CA 92108 | <u>Edgar.Fernand@outlook.com</u> | (360) 932-6524 <u>Github.com/HCTyler</u> | <u>LinkedIn.com/in/edgarvf/</u> | https://hctyler.github.io/Portfolios/

Summary Statement

I am looking for a position that can utilize my knowledge and passion for making accessible and responsive web design as a junior front end developer. I am a service driven individual with over 5 years providing support to customers in a team-based environment.

Skills

HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, SCSS/SASS, Bootstrap, jQuery, React, MySQL, NoSQL

Work Experience

Sharp Healthcare - San Diego, California May 2021- Present Lab Assistant

- Assist with the pre-analytical, analytical, and post-analytical lab processes.
- Communicate effectively with nurses and different departments of the lab in regard to laboratory orders.
- Performs data entry and specimen processing; organize and process orders; checks working material inventory with minimal supervision.
- Research and verifies lab codes are correct

Quest Diagnostics, Seattle, Washington
June 2019 – April 2021
Specimen Technician I/Pre-Analytic Assistant I

- Employee of the Month, Awarded for Positive Attitude and Dedication, January 2020
- Maintained productivity for Specimen Processing with 300+ test processes per day and continuously exceeded Tech Ops. defer metric of 150+ aliquots per hour.
- Was responsible for overseeing closing Tech Ops' department with a team of three associates.
- Complete all assigned data entry assignments within the required timeframe while maintaining a high level of accuracy.

Ross Dress for Less, Seattle, Washington **December 2014- June 2019**

Store Associate

- Employee of the Month in June 2017 and November 2018
- Train new associates on cash office, markdown, cashier,general sales floor maintenance and processing procedures according to company guidelines.
- Routinely helped as many as 100+ customers in the sales floor each day, while balancing the needs of multiple customers simultaneously in a fast-paced retail outlet.
- Process an average of 300+ transactions in registers, while maintaining the company's speed and accuracy expectations.
- Process and stock 4500+ units with high accuracy, exceeding company expectation for productivity and speed per night.
- Responsible for balancing cash registers and the safe daily; preparing daily cash/check deposits and ordering change as needed; keeping records of daily/monthly voided transactions, sales, and till balancing summaries.
- Functioned as Cashier, Fitting Room Associate, Cash Office Associate, Trainer, Markdown Lead, MOD Plus.

Education and Awards

Coding Boot Camp at UC San Diego Extension, September 2021- May 2021

A 24- week course, from the University of California San Diego, that teaches web development skills such as HTLM, CSS, JavaScript, Node.js, Express, MySQL databases, NoSQL Database and React.js.

Associate of Arts Degree, 2019, Seattle Central College, Seattle, WA